Guide to the Labor Union Constitutions, By-Laws and Agreements collection, 1883-1999 LAC0012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Agreements, 1910-1999; Series 2; 7 Linear Feet
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 April 6; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 May 28; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 August 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 October 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Royalmetal Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1962 October 8; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1963; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1963 May 9; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1963 June 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the Phalo Plastics Corporation.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1963 July 26; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1965 September 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1966 February 7; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Agreement with the New York Air Brake Company.
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1968 August 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - United Transportation Union, 1969 May 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - United Transportation Union, 1969 July 1; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Agreement wtih the Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company.
  - United Transportation Union, 1972 January 15; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - United Transportation Union, 1973 January 1; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - United Transportation Union, 1974 December 31; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Beach Education Association Planning Calendar and Memorandum of Understanding, 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wage Scale And Agreement, 1948; Series 2 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Washington Agreement, 1936 May; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 2018 Local #399 Agreement - Studio Transportation Drivers, 1 August 2018; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Agreement between Northwest Airlines and Airline Pilots represented by the Air Line Pilots Association International 1998-2002, Series 2 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, Series 3
  - AFL-CIO compiled Union Pamphlets, 1981; LAC 0012 series 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Rhode Island Papers, 1984; LAC 0012 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - International Typographical Union Correspondence, 1984; LAC 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Strike Letter, 1984; LAC 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Local 635 - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Applications and Legal Documents, 1924-1979; IBT 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Local 635 - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Contracts, 1931-1977; IBT 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Mass Meeting Notice, ND; IBT 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Moving Pictures Union Documents, 1911-1945; LAC 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Notice to Employes - Los Angeles, 1917; IBT 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - PPU Badge, Portland Maine, LAC 0012 Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 10)